Painting Life is a drama film directed by Bijukumar Damodaran.
A Bollywood filmmaker and his crew gets stranded in a remote
Himalayan village due to torrential downpours.
How the intense experiences under siege, affect the filmmaker's
thoughts and priorities forms the central theme of the film.
Filmmaker, played by Prakash Bare.
Nassar, played by Shankar Ramakrishnan.
Wife, played by Meera Vasudevan.
Cinematographer, played by Ravi Singh.
Lady in the guesthouse, played by Geetanjali Thapa.
Painting Life is a 2018 Indian English film written and directed
by Bijukumar Damodaran (commonly known as Dr.
The film was jointly produced by Silicon Media and Blue Ocean Pictures and depicts the
experience of a film crew who are stranded in a remote Himalayan village.
The film explores themes of himalaya mountain
range, stranded, film crew, sikkim.
The tone is emotional and intense.